

Wei-Han Hui (Ambrose)

Email: ambrosehui0105@gmail.com Website: lp65082001.github.io

Tel: (+886) 972106451

Physical modeling and ML/DL application. I have a strong academic background in constructing and applying physical models, particularly in the realm of mathematical modeling, simulation tools, and multiscale simulations. I also have extensive experience in machine learning and deep learning applications, with a track record of successful interdisciplinary collaborations, demonstrating excellent communication and problem-solving skills. In short, I am committed to translating theoretical knowledge into practical applications to solve complex real-world problems.

Experience

09/2019 to 08/2023

Ph.D. project National Taiwan University, Taipei

Physical modeling

- Temperature effect and crosslink effect in collagen.
- Conformation of ion channel and ion pathway.
- Thickness prediction of IMCs layer in Cu-Sn soldering.
- Linear polymer model mapping from atomistic model to coarse-grained model with multi-target parameter fitting.
- Uncovering absorption mechanisms between graphene and small molecule.

ML/DL application

- Protein function prediction with graph neural network.
- Osteogenesis imperfecta lethality prediction with graph neural network.
- Collagen strain prediction with XGboost.

07/2022 to 12/2022

Deep learning intern (object detection) Industrial Technology Research Institute, Hsinchu County

- Unbalanced object detection
- Active learning
- Deploy models on the Google Cloud Platform

Skill Highlights

- Molecular dynamics simulation
 - LAMMPS, NAMD
- Coarse grained model
 - Boltzmann inversion method
- Numerical simulation
 - FEM, FVM
- ML/DL/RL models (methods)
 - XGBoost, SVM
 - CNN, YOLO, GNN
 - GA, CEM
- ML/DL framework
 - Scikit-learn
 - Tensorflow (Keras)
 - Pytorch (Geometric)
- Programming language
 - Python, Matlab, C++

Education

- Ph.D., Artificial Intelligence center of Department of Civil Engineering, National Taiwan University 09/2019-08/2023
- M.S., Department of Civil Engineering, National Taiwan University 09/2017-07/2019
- B.S., Department of Civil Engineering, Chung Yuan Christian University 09/2012-07/2016